KWOK WEI HAO

ASPIRING DATA ANALYST



+65 9222 5692



kwokweihao91@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kwokweihao

https://github.com/Hao22

SUMMARY

As a biomedical sciences major, I have 4 years of experience working as a scientific researcher in clinical genomics and microbiology laboratories. Highly motivated and a lifelong learner, I aspire to utilize my newfound data science skills to transition into a data analyst role.

MY SKILLS

- Python
- SQL
- Git/Github

LANGUAGE:

English (Native)

Mandarin (Native)

WORK EXPERIENCE

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

L'Oréal (Advanced Research) *Sep 2020 - Present*

- Involved in a joint-lab collaboration with Nanyang Technological University to conduct skin and scalp microbiome research.
- Contributed to experiments leading to a novel discovery on scalp microbiome on track for scientific publications.
- Performed statistical analysis and data visualization on generated results with Excel and GraphPad Prism.

RESEARCH OFFICER

Genome Institute of Singapore, A-STAR Aug 2018 - Sep 2020

- Supported validation of clinical assays and clinical samples processing in partnership with hospitals and local institutions.
- Successfully contributed to the development of 3 lab-developed clinical genomics tests which can provide actionable information to patients and doctors.

SENIOR EXECUTIVE (LABORATORY)

Lee Kong Chian School of Medicine *May 2016 - Mar 2018*

- Supported the wet-lab and anatomy practicals for medical students.
- Assisted in setting-up of the Anatomy Resource Center (ARC) which allows students to access information on potted specimens by scanning QR codes.
- Collated experimental results from >100 students and performed data analysis for post-practical discussion sessions.

EDUCATION

DATA SCIENCE IMMERSIVE FLEX

General Assembly 2021 - present

- 24 weeks part time bootcamp to develop the comprehensive skillsets required for successful transition into data science, including Python, SQL, ML, DL, NLP, web scraping and data visualization techniques.
- Completed 4 projects and a capstone project in progress.

B.SC IN BIOMEDICAL SCIENCES (HONS)

• Graduated with 2nd Upper Class Honours

Nanyang Technological University 2012 - 2016